<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Ray Bernard's Fine Tuned Journal</title><link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Ray Bernard's Fine Tuned Journal</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 16:05:44 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Mixture of Agents</title><link>http://localhost:1313/posts/mixture-of-agents/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 16:05:44 -0400</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/mixture-of-agents/</guid><description>How Mixture-of-Agents Enhances Large Language Model Capabilities Introduction In recent years, Large Language Models (LLMs) have significantly advanced the field of natural language understanding and generation. These models, pre-trained on vast datasets and fine-tuned to align with human preferences, have demonstrated impressive capabilities. However, the rapid growth in the number of LLMs and their diverse strengths has presented a new challenge: how to effectively harness the collective expertise of multiple LLMs.</description></item><item><title/><link>http://localhost:1313/posts/llama3-updated/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/llama3-updated/</guid><description>Fine-Tuning LLaMa 3 8B Instruct on Intel Max Series GPUs: An Exciting Journey In this guide, we embark on an exciting journey to fine-tune the powerful LLaMa 3 8B Instruct model using a custom dataset on Intel Max Series GPUs. Intel GPUs offer incredible speed and cost-effectiveness, making them an attractive choice for training large language models.
I successfully trained the LLaMa 3 8B Instruct model using my custom dataset, leveraging the power of HuggingFace.</description></item><item><title/><link>http://localhost:1313/posts/open-webui-moa-groq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/open-webui-moa-groq/</guid><description>Open WebUI MoA Groq Introduction The Mixture-of-Agents (MoA) methodology has demonstrated state-of-the-art performance using open-source models, as detailed in my previous blog. We have created two pipelines (Groq and Ollama) for Open-WebUI. These pipelines serve as versatile, UI-agnostic OpenAI-compatible plugin frameworks.
In this blog, we will demonstrate how MoA can be integrated into Open WebUI, an extensible, feature-rich, and user-friendly self-hosted WebUI designed to operate entirely offline. Open WebUI supports various LLM runners, including Ollama and OpenAI-compatible APIs.</description></item></channel></rss>